# Chris Ginter

ginteruf@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

I built my first website in high school - a GeoCities tribute page to the band 311. The novelty of that experience led me to enroll in a computer programming class that summer at a nearby college. I was enthralled by it. It was the perfect mix of creativity and logic, leveraged by enormous computational power.

After being a freelance web developer for several years, I got the itch to start a company. Entrepreneurship is intriguing to me for many of the same reasons as programming. Starting with a blank slate and having to iteratively build a complex system through sheer determination. I cofounded a startup in the commercial HVAC space in 2013 and participated in the accelerator program Y Combinator in 2014.

# **SKILLS**

- Ruby on Rails
- HTML
- PostgreSQL

- React
- CSS
- Linux

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Ravti

01 / 2013 - Present

Cofounder

Architected and developed 50k LOC Ruby on Rails codebase. Migrated front-end from Ruby templates to React. Setup and maintained Linode VPS. Later responsible for interviewing, hiring, and managing a team.

#### MyMedLab

11 / 2011 - 05 / 2014

Full stack developer

Led development on existing 100k LOC Ruby on Rails 2 codebase. Responsible for bug fixes, new features, and server administration. Upgraded codebase from Rails 2 to 3.

## **EDUCATION**

## University of Florida

2002 - 2007

Bachelor's Degree , Computer Science

UF Honors Program

#### **INTERESTS**

Entrepreneurship, personal development, nutrition, golf, snowboarding

# LANGUAGES

• English ( Native or bilingual proficiency )